Madeline Frank Collection 087
DCPL Special Collections - MLK Library
Madeline Frank Collection
1905-1906
DCPL Special Collections - MLK Library
Frank, Madeline Harriet
087
0.25 Linear feet
1 Boxes
Arrangement
Processed without series.
Biographical / Historical
After graduating from Lafayette High School in Buffalo, NY, Madeline Harriet Frank attended the Washington College for Young Ladies in D.C. from 1905-1906. She studied music, French, 19th century literature, education, mythology and art history, and was a member of the Sigma Theta Delta sorority.
Custodial History
This collection was donated to the DC Public Library in 1997.
Scope and Contents
This collection consists of photos, clippings, correspondence, and a copy of the Washington College handbook, as well as a diary titled The College Girl's Record, which includes images, clippings, invitations, and Madeline Frank's impressions of Washington College and her classmates.
Women; Education, higher; Correspondence; Photographs; Ephemera; Diaries
- Series 1
  - Ephemera (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Photos - Classmates and class trips, 1905-1906 (Item 1)
    - Letter regarding Sigma Theta Delta, 1905 (Item 2)
    - Letter to Mrs. Celia Frank from Washington College regarding Madeline, 1905 (Item 3)
    - Tuition Receipt, 1905 (Item 4)
    - Poem, undated (Item 5)
    - Calling cards, undated (Item 6)
    - Clippings, 1906 (Item 7)
    - Washington College handbook, 1905 (Item 8)